James Maduka

Software Developer & Tester

Summary

I am a software developer with over three years of experience in testing, development, and maintenance of web, mobile and desktop solutions.

I have proven capacity both as an independent contractor and a strategic development partner, working on projects for/with individuals, startups, and other agencies.

I have facilitated the development of over five multiple projects and have single-handedly driven the development of most of these projects.

Experience

Independent Contractor – FEB 2018 – till date **Software Tester**

TESTIO | TESTERWORK, Bangalore, India

• Executed test case, perform exploratory test and report bugs/defects to the team lead.

Independent Contractor – FEB 2019 – till date **Software Developer**

GORLAS, Lagos, Nigeria

- Successfully implemented and deployed web-based application and web API using Python, Flask, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, MySQL.
- Implemented and deployed mobile and desktop applications using Kivy, Flask, Python, MySQL.
- Designed, developed user flow for a Telegram and WhatsApp bot using python, flask, Django, Twilio and deployed to cloud servers Heroku and Digital Ocean.

Independent Contractor –JAN 2020 – till date **Web Developer**

RABIT CONSULTING, Lagos, Nigeria

- Successfully implemented and deployed internal and external web-based applications and web API using Python, PHP, Django, JavaScript, CSS, HTML, MySQL and Reactjs.
- Handled the development of web app prototypes for presentations.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Application (BCA): 2015 - 2018

Bangalore university, Karnataka, India

Senior Secondary School Certificate (WAEC/SSCE): 2011 - 2014 Top highflyer secondary school, Lagos, Nigeria Social

Contact

in 💆 📮 💿

<u>+234 (814) 608-9071</u> jamesdaniel00700@gmail.com

Bio Data

Date of birth: 26th July 1997

Gender: Male

Marital Status: Single

Skills

- CSS
- Flask
- Django
- HTML
- JavaScript & jQuery
- MySQL
- Kivy
- Reactjs
- PHP
- Python